Unemployment is low by
historic standards.
So why are so many project
managers and analysts
sending out hundreds
of applications and hearing
nothing back these days?
The truth is, the market's
changed.
AI is reshaping how employers
screen and select candidates,
and applications that
reflect true authenticity
are outperforming cold
applications.
Join us at a free PMI
South Florida Lunch and
Learn on Wednesday, July
29th, at noon, where
you'll learn more about
the job search tactics
that are working today,
and that can help you
get hired, stand out,
and demonstrate your
value.
Please register at the
link in the post.
See you then!